Uurtsaikh Nyambat

Software Developer / DevOps engineer

+976 8666 6217 • vvrtsaix.n@gmail.com • Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia • Portfolio site • Linkedin

Profile

With five years of experience in Software Development and DevOps, I've honed my skills across a diverse range of applications and systems. My passion for collaboration and strong software development abilities have made me a respected team player. I hold a particular interest in backend, full-stack development, and DevOps engineering.

Certifications

CKA: Certified Kubernetes Administrator

Linux Foundation

AWS Certified Solutions Architect – Associate

Amazon Web Services

Work Experience

Senior Lead Software Developer, Monosolution LLC

Feb 2023 - Now

- As a Development Team Lead, I spearheaded two projects. The first, 'Detect HCC,' is a Clinical Research Management System has real-time communication (including chat, video, and phone), file system, and comprehensive clinical study capabilities. The second project, the 'Business Management System (BMS),' boasts features such as communication tools, file system, company newsfeed, HR, and CRM.
- I trained my peers and used DevOps CI/CD.
- Technologies: NodeJS, GraphQL, TailwindCSS, React, GoLang, NextJS, Flutter, MQTT and Microservice

Chief Cloud Architect, Fibo Cloud Pte Ltd.

Feb 2022 - Feb 2023

- My role involved researching and developing features and services for public clouds, including cloud.mn and cloud.ttc.kz. I made significant contributions to the creation of Managed Kubernetes Service and App platform, as well as Simplehost for PHP-based applications.
- I provided valuable DevOps and cloud service consulting services to other companies.
- I instructed courses on Kubernetes and container technology.

Senior Software Engineer, TECH PARTNERS

Jun 2021 - Feb 2023

- I've had the privilege of working on diverse projects, including leading the development team for the travel website ITrip.mn, contributing to the Yuna restaurant app, and developing the student management system for Citi University.
- Technologies: GoLang, React, NextJS, Flutter, tRPC, gRPC, TailwindCSS and DotNet

Senior Software Engineer, Fibo Cloud Pte Ltd,

Jun 2020 - Feb 2022

- I've played a pivotal role in diverse projects, including the Fibo Stack Private Cloud Management System, the Mongolian Public Cloud Service (Cloud.mn), and consulting on public cloud (AWS, GCP, Azure) and DevOps.
- Technologies: AWS, GCP, Docker, Kubernetes, Linux, Openstack, Jenkins, Gitlab CI, GoLang, gRPC, React and Python

Full Stack Engineer, Eclinic

Jul 2020 - Dec 2020

- I was part of a three-engineer team that developed an ERP system for a hospital.
- Technologies: Laravel (PHP), Vue (Javascript) and Java spring (Java)

Skills

Software development (5 years)

Team management (3 years)

Cloud Solutions Architect (3 years)

System Architecture (3 years)

DevOps (3 years)

Mobile Application Developer, Codocore

Jun 2020 - Jul 2020

- I've worked on two React Native applications. The first is a mobile job app with separate interfaces for employees and employers. It's powered by a WordPress backend with GraphQL integration. The second is a nurse rental app.
- Technologies: React Native, Wordpress and GraphQL

Education

Bachelor's degree in Computer Software Engineering

2016 - 2020 - Mongolian University of Science and Technology

Languages

Mongolian - Native

English - Intermediate